nice to meet you.
初めまして
I know you're nervous.
緊張してるのはわかるよ
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Hey.
ねえ
It’s your first time, right?
初めてでしょ?
It was about half a year ago that I yelled at you.
ぶっ声かけたん、もう半年ぐらい前だった?
Yeah.
うん
You've finally come.
やっと来てくれたね
How was it?
どうでした?
Somehow, I changed my mind.
なんか、考えが変わったんです
a little bit.
ちょっと
Yeah.
うん
How did you come back?
どう して帰った?
I don't know all of a sudden.
急にわかんないです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I'm really happy about it.
僕にとっちゃ嬉しいんですけど
Yeah.
うん
Sister, your legs are long.
お 姉さん、足長いっすね
How tall are you now?
今、身長、おいくつですか?
Yeah.
うん
It's about 30.
30ぐらいです
Ah, that's right.
あっ、そんなんですね
Body?
身体?
Something like 43.
43とか
intuition.
かん
It's late.
遅いね
Favorite type?
好きなタイプ?
Yeah.
うん
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏さんいらっしゃるんですか?
I thought there would definitely be one.
絶対いると思ってた
Such a cute child.
こんな可愛い子は
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いよ
Isn't it possible to become an idol?
アイドルいけるんじゃない?
Have you never thought about aiming for it?
目指そうと思ったことない?
Not really.
ないね
What kind of work are you doing now?
今、お仕事なんてされてるんですか?
Yeah.
うん
I have a part-time job.
バイトしてます
Oh, it's a cafe.
あ、カフェってね
I'm so happy.
嬉しいですよね
current situation
今の状況
teeth.
は
I'm glad you said that about our work, too.
僕 らのこの仕事もね、 言ってくれて嬉しいんだけど、
It makes your face look better.
顔張りが良くするんでね
If you're such a cute girl, what if something happens to you?
こんな可愛い子ならね、 何かあった時はね、
Please tell me.
言ってください
Maybe I should ask you a mean question.
意地悪な質問しちゃおうかな
When was the last time you had sex?
最近エッチしたのがいつですか?
About half a year ago.
半年前ぐらい
Really?
ガチで?
How many people have experience?
経験人数?
That's right.
そんなね
is that so.
そうですか
Well then, I'm going to go with my uncle now in the car.
じゃあね、今からおじさんとね、 車の中で、
I think I'll do something I've never done before,
私は経験したこともないことすると思うんだけど、
What in particular?
何だって特になの?
I'm not good at it.
苦手です
Oh, are you not good at it?
あ、苦手ですか
It's here, just a little bit.
ここんだね、ちょっとね
got it.
わかりました
I want to back away from the princess, so can I come a little closer to you?
姫さんを背退したいんで、 ちょっと近づいていいですか?
Can I just ask you to take off your mask now?
そ ろそろマスクだけ取ってもらっていいですか?
nice.
いい ね
After all, I'm jealous of my boyfriend.
や っぱり、 彼氏さん羨ましいわ
Well, just a little bit.
もうね、ちょっとだって